One moment can change everything
Felony is a mystery, thriller, crime film directed by Matthew Saville.
Three detectives become embroiled in a tense struggle after a tragic
accident that leaves a child in critical condition.
One is guilty of a crime, one will try to cover it up,
and the other attempts to expose it.
How far will these men go to disguise and unravel the truth?
Detective Malcolm Toohey, played by Joel Edgerton.
Detective Jim Melic, played by Jai Courtney.
Julie Toohey, played by Melissa George.
Detective Carl Summer, played by Tom Wilkinson.
Ankhila Sarduka, played by Sarah Roberts.
Patient, played by Alex Haddad.
Felony is a 2013 Australian crime thriller film directed by Matthew Saville.
Joel Edgerton wrote, produced and co-starred in the film.
Tom Wilkinson, Jai Courtney, and Melissa George also appeared in the film.
It was screened in the Special Presentation section at the
2013 Toronto International Film Festival.
The film explores themes of australia, police, hit-and-run, dirty cop, accident.
The tone is mind_bending and intense.